<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Defs>
 
  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>Force_LightSide</defName>
    <label>Light-Side</label>
    <description>Master the light side of the Force to cast abilities that heal, protect, and support allies.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/Lightside</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_Lightside</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>The light side of the Force was concerned with the ideals of good, benevolence, and healing. Followers of the light side strove to live in harmony with the world around them, acting out of wisdom and logic rather than anger and hasty judgment.</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>

  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>Force_Neutral</defName>
    <label>Force-Sensitive</label>
    <description>Master the Force to maintain balance and harmony, using abilities that neither align with the light nor the dark side.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/Neutral</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_Neutral</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>The Force Sensitive was a being who was highly attuned to the flow of the Force. Force-sensitives could, with training, learn to sense and manipulate the Force. Force-sensitives who gained powers and abilities through the Force became Force Adepts.</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
  
  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>Force_Darkside</defName>
    <label>Dark-Side</label>
    <description>Master the dark side of the Force to cast abilities that harm, dominate, and destroy enemies.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/Darkside</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_Darkside</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>The dark side of the Force was considered by the Jedi to be the element aligned with selfishness, fear, hatred, aggression, and malice toward all living things. Such emotions seemed to increase the strength and abilities of a user of the dark side, providing a path towards personal power and the destruction or control of all opposition.</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
  
  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>Force_SithSorcery</defName>
    <label>Sith Sorcery</label>
    <description>Master the arcane arts of the Sith to manipulate the dark side of the Force through spells and rituals.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/SithSorcerer</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_SithSorcery</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>Through the recitation of spells, execution of hand gestures, and/or the handling of various artifacts, darksiders were able to channel the raw power of the Force's malignant side to warp minds, alter the environment, and obliterate whatever obstacles stood in their way.</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
  
  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>Force_Telekinesis</defName>
    <label>Telekinesis</label>
    <description>Master the Force to push, pull, and manipulate objects and enemies with telekinetic power.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/Telekinesis</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_Telekinesis</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>"A Jedi traditionally uses telekinesis to move inanimate objects, but there are some occasions when one might be forced to use this ability on an enemy combatant" - Luke Skywalker</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
  
  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>Force_JediTraining</defName>
    <label>Jedi Training</label>
    <description>Undergo rigorous Jedi training to enhance your abilities and improve your connection to the Force.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/JediTraining</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_JediTraining</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>Jedi training was the action of teaching an apprentice the ways of the Force in the Jedi Order. Focusing on longer casting for longer buffs, start off with improving oneself, then move on to improving others with your skills.</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>

  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>Force_LightsaberCombat</defName>
    <label>Lightsaber Combat</label>
    <description>Master the art of lightsaber combat to unleash powerful melee attacks and disable your opponents. Requires a melee weapon to use.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/JediTraining</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_LightsaberCombat</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>"Energy constantly flows through the crystal. You're not fighting with a simple blade as much as you are directing a current of power. Your thoughts, your actions, they become energy. They flow through the crystal as well and become a part of the blade." - Kanan Jarrus</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>

</Defs>