<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Defs>
 
  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>VPE_LightSide</defName>
    <label>Light-Side</label>
    <description>Harness the power of the Force to cast unique abilities.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/Lightside</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_Lightside</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>The light side of the Force was concerned with the ideals of good, benevolence, and healing. Followers of the light side strove to live in harmony with the world around them, acting out of wisdom and logic rather than anger and hasty judgment.</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>

  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>VPE_Force</defName>
    <label>Force-Sensitive</label>
    <description>Harness the power of the Force to cast unique abilities.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/Neutral</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_Neutral</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>The Force Sensitive was a being who was highly attuned to the flow of the Force. Force-sensitives could, with training, learn to sense and manipulate the Force. Force-sensitives who gained powers and abilities through the Force became Force Adepts.</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
  
  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>VPE_Darkside</defName>
    <label>Dark-Side</label>
    <description>Harness the power of the Force to cast unique abilities.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/Darkside</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_Darkside</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>The dark side of the Force was considered by the Jedi to be the element aligned with selfishness, fear, hatred, aggression, and malice toward all living things. Such emotions seemed to increase the strength and abilities of a user of the dark side, providing a path towards personal power and the destruction or control of all opposition</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
  
  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>VPE_SithSorcery</defName>
    <label>Sith Sorcery</label>
    <description>An arcane expression of Force ability first developed and practiced by the original Sith species through which they manipulated the power of the dark side.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/Darkside</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_Darkside</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>Through the recitation of spells, execution of hand gestures, and/or the handling of various artifacts, darksiders were able to channel the raw power of the Force's malignant side to warp minds, alter the environment, and obliterate whatever obstacles stood in their way.</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
  
  <VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
    <defName>VPE_Telekinesis</defName>
    <label>Telekinesis</label>
    <description>Harness the power of the Force to push and pull your enemies.</description>
    <background>UI/Backgrounds/Telekinesis</background>
    <altBackground>UI/AlternativeBackgrounds/PathBG_Telekinesis</altBackground>
    <tab>Force Powers</tab>
    <tooltip>"A Jedi traditionally uses telekinesis to move inanimate objects, but there are some occasions when one might be forced to use this ability on an enemy combatant" - Luke Skywalker</tooltip>
  </VanillaPsycastsExpanded.PsycasterPathDef>
  

  
</Defs>